A Guide to Records of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1995-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Agency Correspondence, 2006-2009., Extent: 25 boxes. (Box 16-40)
  - VEDP Conference on World Trade. (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - VEDP Constituent Correspondence. (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - VEDP Continental. (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - VEDP Corning, Inc. (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - VEDP Covance. (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - VEDP CQ--Commerce Quarterly. (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - VEDP Continuity of Operations (COOP). (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - VEDP Crown Cork & Seal. (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - VEDP CSC. (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - VEDP CSX Mega Site (Emporia-Greensville). (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - VEDP Dahlgren. (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - VEDP DARPA. (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - VEDP Data Centers. (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - VEDP DBA Study. (Box 31, Folder 38-41)
  - VEDP Danville--Economic Development Trip. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - VEDP DeRoyal Industries. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - VEDP Digimarc. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - VEDP Diversified Information Technologies. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - VEDP Dominion Resources. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - VEDP Dominion VA Power, SCC Public Hearing. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - VEDP Draper Center of Excellence. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - VEDP Dupont. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - VEDP DuPont Fabros Technologies. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - VEDP Eastern Microfilm Imaging. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - VEDP Economic Development Strategic Plan. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - VEDP EDO and Paris. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - VEDP EDS. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - VEDP Eli Lilly and Company. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - VEDP El Salvador. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - VEDP Employment Creation and Capital Investment in Virginia Report. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - VEDP Energy. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - VEDP Enterprise Zone. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - VEDP Equitable. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - VEDP E-Star Award. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - VEDP Essel Propack. (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - VEDP Executive Pulse. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - VEDP Expense Reports. (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - VEDP Federal Express. (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - VEDP Fenner Dunlop (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - VEDP Finance Committee. (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - VEDP Financial Statements. (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - VEDP Forbes.com "Virginia: The Best State for Business." (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - VEDP Foreign Trade Barriers (H1N1 Influenza Outbreak). (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - VEDP Fortune Magazine. (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - VEDP 4-Peat Luncheon at Capitol, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - VEDP GE. (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - VEDP General. (Box 32, Folder 33-34)
  - VEDP Genworth Financial, Inc. (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - VEDP Global Logic. (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - VEDP Goodyear. (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - VEDP Google, Inc. (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - VEDP WM GreenTech Automotive Corporation (EB-5). (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - VEDP GreenTech Reclamation Services. (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - VEDP General Services Administration (GSA). (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - VEDP Gubernatorial Presentationn. (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - VEDP Gwathmey, Inc. (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - VEDP Hampton Roads Economic Development Alliance (HREDA). (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - VEDP Harris Interactive Executive Omnibus Survey. (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - VEDP Headquarters Marketing. (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - VEDP Hilton Hotels (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - VEDP Ibiden Co. Ltd. (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - VEDP IBO--International Baccalaureate Organization. (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - VEDP Ikea Gropu (Swedwood International AB) (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - VEDP InBev. (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - VEDP Incentives. (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - VEDP Incentives (Guidelines for Econ. Dev. Incentive Programs). (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - VEDP IGNITE Institute for Individualized Health. (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - VEDP India. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - VEDP INDIA (Vibrant Gujarat: Global Investor's Summit, 2009). (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - VEDP Infeneon Technologies, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - VEDP Innovation. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - VEDP International Asset Management Council (IAMC). (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - VEDP International Trade Division (Focus Group Meetings). (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - VEDP International Travel Schedule. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - VEDP Intrexon Corporation. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - VEDP Embassy of Ireland. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - VEDP ITIF-Kauffman 2007 State New Economy Index. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - VEDP Jack Henry & Associates. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - VEDP Jacoby Development. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - VEDP JAFZA International. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - VEDP Jefferson Lab. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - VEDP Kent Count Council England. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - VEDP Koch Industries. (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - VEDP Kolmar (Project Lilac). (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - VEDP Korea. (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - VEDP LabCorp. (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - VEDP Lear. (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - VEDP Lee County. (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - VEDP Legislation. (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - VEDP Level 3 Communications. (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - VEDP LiFeBATT, Inc. USA. (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - VEDP Loudoun County. (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - VEDP Loudoun County Extension. (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - VEDP Luciad, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - VEDP LUNA Innovations. (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - VEDP Luxembourg. (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - VEDP Magna Steyr AG Project (Town of St. Paul). (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - VEDP Manufacturing Impact and Economic Diversification Plan FY 2007-2011. (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - VEDP Marketing Travel Approvals. (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - VEDP MARS North America. (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - VEDP Martinsville Henry County Virginia Economic Development Corporation (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - VEDP Life Sciences/Bioscience Study-Maryland. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - VEDP McQuary International. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - VEDP Meadowville Interchange. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - VEDP MeadWestvaco. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - VEDP Mega Project Advisory Group. (Box 34, Folder 5-7)
  - VEDP Merk and Company. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - VEDP Micron Technology, Inc. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - VEDP Mid Atlantic Bio Conference. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - VEDP Mirbeau Inn & Spa. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - VEDP Mitsubishi Gas Chemical. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - VEDP Mondo USA. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - VEDP GOF--General. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - VEDP GOF--Money Committee (General). (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - VEDP VIP--Money Committee (General). (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - VEDP VEDIG Guidelines--Money Committee. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - VEDP GOF--Money Committee (Quarterly). (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - GOF--Money Committee (Bi-Annual). (Box 34, Folder 19-21)
  - VEDP Monocan Indian Nation. (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - VEDP MTU Detroit Diesel, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - VEDP MZM Project. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - VEDP NAACP. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - VEDP NEW Asurion. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - VEDP New York, New York, 2006. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - VEDP Norfolk Southern. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - VEDP Northrup Grumman. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - VEDP Northrup Grumman (MOI - Advanced Shipbuilding Training Facility Grant Program). (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - VEDP NVTC. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - VEDP Nypro, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - VEDP Orbital Sciences Corporation. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - VEDP Operating Plan. (Box 35, Folder 12-13)
  - VEDP Patrick County. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - VEDP Pepper's Ferry Regional Watewater Treatment Authority. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - VEDP Performance Fibers. (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - VEDP Pfizer. (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - VEDP Philip Morris USA Inc. (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - VEDP Pioneer Hospital (Patrick County). (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - VEDP Ply Gem Industries, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - VEDP Poland. (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - VEDP Polymer Group. (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - VEDP Poplar Hill. (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - VEDP Praxair. (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - VEDP Premier Woodworking. (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - VEDP Press Releases. (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - VEDP PrimeStar Solar, Inc. (Project Sunshine). (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - VEDP Printing Authorizations. (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - VEDP Progenitor Cell Therapy, LLC. (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - VEDP Project Apricus. (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - VEDP Project Eagle. (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - VEDP Project Grand. (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - VEDP Project Longspur. (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - VEDP Project Tiger. (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - VEDP Projects in the Pipeline Report. (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - VEDP QIMONDA North America. (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - VEDP Rail Barge Access. (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - VEDP Raytheon. (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - VEDP Ready Corporation. (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - VEDP Renewables. (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - VEDP Research and the Regional Economy: The Research University as a Driver. (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - VEDP Roanoke Region Intermodal. (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - VEDP Roanoke Valley-Alleghany Regional Commission. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - VEDP Rolls Royce (US Air Force Tanker Project). (Box 36, Folder 2-4)
  - VEDP Rolls-Royce North America Project Corvette. (Box 36, Folder 5-7)
  - VEDP Rolls-Royce North America (Transaction Documents) (Box 36, Folder 8-10)
  - VEDP RTI International Metals (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - VEDP Rural Economic Development Strategic Plan, 2006. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - VEDP Sallie Mae. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - VEDP Scheduling. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - VEDP Science Applications International Corporation (SAIC). (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - VEDP Semiconductor Manufacturing Performance Grant Payments (Micron Technology/Qimonda). (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - VEDP Shenandoah Life/One America. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - VEDP Silynx Communications, Inc. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - VEDP Single Sales Factor. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - VEDP Skybus. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - VEDP Smallbone (Project Goliath). (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - VEDP Smithfield Foods. (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - VEDP Smorgan Steel (Project Orange). (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - VEDP Solar Panels Plus. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - VEDP Sprint. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - VEDP SRI. (Box 37, Folder 16-19)
  - SRI/Virginia University Researh Partnership (VURP). (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - VEDP SRI International/Virginia University Research Partnership (VURP). (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - VEDP SRI VURP. (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Virginia University Research Partnership (VURP). (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - VEDP State Plane Requests. (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - VEDP Strauss North America. (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - VEDP SteelFab of Virginia, Inc. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - VEDP SVC Manufacturing, Inc. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - VEDP Taiwan. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - VEDP Tata Sons Limited. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - VEDP Tax Competitiveness. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - VEDP Department of Taxation. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - VEDP TBC Corporation. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - VEDP Teekay Shipping. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - VEDP Terremark. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - VEDP TEVA Pharmaceutical Industries. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - VEDP Texturing Services, Inc. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - VEDP TheraGauze. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - VEDP Theranostics Health (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - VEDP Think North America. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - VEDP Third Security, LLC. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - VEDP TMEIC GE. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - VEDP Tobacco Grants. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - VEDP Toray Carbon Fibers America, Inc. (Project V2008). (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - VEDP Toyota. (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - VEDP Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund (TPOF). (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - VEDP Governor Kaine's Foreign Trade And Marketing Missions. (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - VEDP State Department Training Center. (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - VEDP TransTech Pharma, LLC. (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - VEDP Travel Authorizations. (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - VEDP Twin Creeks Technologies. (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - VEDP TYCO Electronics. (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - VEDP University Research Group. (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - VEDP VASCIC. (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - VEDP Virginia Business Publication Special Section. (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - VEDP Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU). (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - VEDP Virginia Immunology Center. (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - VEDP VA Tech/Arlington/IBM. (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - VEDP VA Tobacco Commission. (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - VEDP VITAL. (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - VEDP Volkswagen. (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - VEDP Volvo. (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - VEDP Wachovia Securities. (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - VEDP Waterford Furniture Makers. (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - VEDP Waverly Particleboard Co. (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - VEDP Wellborn Cabinet (Ashland, AL). (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - VEDP West Coast Marketing Trip, 2008. (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - VEDP Westinghouse Electric Company LLC Nuclear Project. (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - VEDP White Birch. (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - VEDP WIA Discretionary Funds (supporting CGI Technologies and Solutions, Inc. Expansion. (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - VEDP Wolseley Project. (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - VEDP Workforce. (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - VEDP Wytheville. (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - VEDP Project Zenzu. (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - VEDP Trade Missions, 2006-2009. (Box 39, Folder 1-12)
  - VEDP Various Trips, 2006-2009. (Box 40, Folder 1-12)
- Series IV: Special Projects and Studies, 2006-2009., Extent: 12 boxes. (Box 41-46, 70-71, 91-94)
  - Special Assistant Christine Simpson Special Projects. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary Vivek Kundra Special Projects. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary Alleyn Harned Special Projects. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary Alex Daniel Special Projects. (Box 44-45)
  - Deputy Secretary David Smith Special Projects (Box 46)
  - Economic Crisis Strike Force, 2006. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Governor Kaine's Economic Development Strategic Plan,2006-2008. (Box 70, Folder 2-10)
  - Virginia Energy Plan, 2006-2007. (Box 71, Folder 1-7)
  - Ford-Norfolk, 2006-2007. (Box 71, Folder 8-10)
  - Ford Motor Company-Dearborn, Michigan, 2006. (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - International Paper Plant Closure (Franklin), 2009. (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Renew Virginia Initiative, 2008-2009. (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Germany--Transatlantic Climate Bridge Agreement, 2008-2009. (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - United Kingdom--Global Climate Change Action, 2009. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Deputy Secretary Rick Seger Special Projects. (Box 91)
  - Transportation Partnership Opportunity Fund, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Hampton Roads Broadband Netowrk, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership Draft Operating Plan FY09, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth Account Policies and Procedures, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Virginia's Apportionment Formula, 2005. (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Sustainable Community Investment, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Report on Business Incentives, 2007-2008. (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Report on Statewide Management and Compliance, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Employment, 2007-2008. (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Opportunity Fund, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - SRI Shenandoah Valley, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - VEDP-Catalyzing Innovation in the Commonwealth, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Virginia is for Business, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Wildernesss Area Proposals, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Pepper's Ferry Regional Wastewater Treatment Authority, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Chesapeake Ethanol Refinery, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Mega Projects Working Group, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Southeastern Virginia Partnership for Regional Transformation, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Opportunity, Inc. of Hampton Roads, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company, 2006. (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - SRI International, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Quarterly Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Commercial Space Flight Authority, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - The Governor's Cabinet Secretaries, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Virginia-Headquartered Insurance Companies, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Norfolk Ford Plant Closure, 2006. (Box 92, Folder 27-29)
  - Lear--Strasburg, 2006. (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Barter Theatre, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Uranium, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - Engle Homes, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - Blue Ribbon Review Panel, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - Advanced Placement Iniatiative, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Dodd and Associates Surveyors, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Tourism, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 37)
  - Rural Broadband Initiative, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 38)
  - WIRED, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 39)
  - VITA, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 40)
  - Uniform Accident Prevention Program, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 41)
  - Quarterly Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 42)
  - Outlying Fields, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 43)
  - Resource Allocation Task Force, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 44)
  - Systems Integration, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 45)
  - Gov's Tech & Engineering Academies, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 46)
  - VEC Issues, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 47)
  - WIA MOU Team, 2006-2007. (Box 92, Folder 48)
  - National Interests Corridor, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 49)
  - FMFADA, 2007. (Box 92, Folder 50)
  - DBA Study, 2008. (Box 92, Folder 51)
  - Budget, 2007. (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
  - MOU Signature, 2007. (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Special Projects, 2004-2008. (Box 93, Folder 3-9)
  - Strategic Plan, 2006. (Box 93, Folder 10-12)
  - TPOF, 2006-2007. (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - I-95/395 BRT/Hot Lanes, 2006. (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Coalfields Expressway, 2006. (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - TPOF General Information, 2005-2006. (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Route 28 Interchanges, 2006. (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - VPA: Heartland Corridor, 2006. (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - TPOF, 2006. (Box 93, Folder 19-20)
  - Workforce Development, 2009. (Box 94, Folder 1-3)
  - SRI International, 2007. (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - VA Board of Accountancy-Toyota Motor Company, 2006-2007. (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - VEDP, 2009. (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - DHS HQ, 2006. (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - SteelFab, 2006. (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - DuPont, 2007. (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - De Bioderij Project, 2006. (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Volvo Truck, 1999-2006. (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Data Center Taxation 2006. (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Venture Capital, 2006. (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - DPOR, 2007. (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - DPOR/Regulatory Issues, 2006. (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Piedmont Environmental Council, 2006. (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - DMME, 2007. (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Mine Improvement and Emergency Response Act, 2006. (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Offshore Energy, 2006. (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - VA Energy Plan, 2006-2007. (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Energy, 2004-2007. (Box 94, Folder 21-23)
  - Virginia Occupational Safety and Health Program, 2007. (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Dept. of Labor and Industry, 2007. (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - VOSH Regulations/Public, 2006. (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Registered Apprenticeship, 2007. (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Executive Order No. 107, 2009. (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - OSHSPA, 2007. (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - DBA Consolidation Study, 2008. (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - Galax, 2008. (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 2007-2008. (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - WIRED, 2009. (Box 94, Folder 33)
  - VEDP Agency Strategic Plan, 2009. (Box 94, Folder 34)
  - Department of Housing and Community Development, 2009. (Box 94, Folder 35)
  - Economic Crisis Strike Force, 2009. (Box 94, Folder 36)
  - Programs, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 37)
- Series V: Public Relations, Activities, and Events, 2006-2009., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 47-50)
  - Speaking Engagements,Jan.-Oct.2006. (Box 47)
  - Speaking Engagements,Nov. 2006-Apr. 2008. (Box 48)
  - Speaking Engagements,May 2008-Feb. 2009. (Box 49)
  - Speaking Engagements,Mar. 2009-Jan. 2010. (Box 50)
- Series VI: Development Projects and Initiatives, 2006-2009., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 51-52, 72, 78)
  - BRAC Arlington. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - BRAC Belvoir. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - BRAC Dahlgren. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - BRAC Ft. Monroe. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Ft. Monroe. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - BRAC General. (Box 51, Folder 6-9)
  - BRAC VNDIA. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - BRAC Grants, 2007. (Box 51, Folder 11-13)
  - BRAC. (Box 52, Folder 1-4)
  - BRAC Fort Monroe Site Assessment. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - BRAC U.S. Air Force - Air Force Cyber Command Headquarters (AFCYBER). (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - BRAC Inter-Agency Task Force. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - BRAC Navy Environment Impact Statement (EIS), Mayport, FL. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Military Relations (Headquarters of Air Force Cyber Command) - City of Hampton. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Military Relations (BAE Systems - Manassas). (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Military Relations - U.S. Army. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - BRAC Office of Economic Adjustment (OEA). (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Department of Defense - Office of Economic Adjustment. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - BRAC Outlying Landing Field (OLF). (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act (Funding Requests), 2009 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act (ARRA) (Economic Stimulus), 2009 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - 2009 (Box 72)
  - ARRA Economic Stimulus, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 4-7)
  - Decision Briefs,2006-2008. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Decision Briefs,2008-2009. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Decision Briefs,2009. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Decision Briefs,2009-2010. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Business One Stop, 2007-2008. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Workforce Development (Meeting of the States), 2007. (Box 78, Folder 2-3)
  - Workforce Development, 2006-2008. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Workforce Development, 2003-2006. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Workforce Development, 2003. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Workforce Development, 2003-2006. (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Workforce Development Strategic Plan, 2006. (Box 78, Folder 8-10)
- Series VII: Secretary's Correspondence, 2006-2009., Extent: 13 boxes. (Box 53-63, 66-67)
  - Fort Monroe Federal Area Redevelopment Authority (FMFADA). (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - FMFADA Approval to Hire Accounting/Finance Temp. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - FMFADA Approval for Job Description for Finance Director. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - FMFADA Board Appointments. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - FMFADA Cooperation Agreement. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - FMFADA Directions. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - FMFADA General Correspondence. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - FMFADA Historic Preservation Advisory Group. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - FMFADA Memorandum of Agreement. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - FMFADA Parking Decal Information. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - FMFADA Reuse Plan. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - FMFADA RFPs-Special Needs Assessments. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - FMFADA RFP for Coordinator--Long Range Interpretive Master Plan. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - FMFADA Briefing Meeting, April 9, 2007. (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - FMFADA Meeting, May 21, 2007. (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - FMFADA Board Meetings, 2007. (Box 53, Folder 16-21)
  - FMFADA Board Meetings, 2008. (Box 53, Folder 22-30)
  - FMFADA Board Meetings, 2009. (Box 54, Folder 1-6)
  - Fort Monroe Planning Steering Committee. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Foreclosure Prevention, 2007-2009. (Box 54, Folder 8-22)
  - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation. (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change, 2008. (Box 55, Folder 3-8)
  - Sub-Cabinet on Community Investment. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Developmet and Land Use Tools. (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
  - Joint Committee Studying Private Institutions Addressing Virginia's Education and Workforce Needs. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Governor's Energy Policy Advisory Council. (Box 55, Folder 13-14)
  - Interagency Task Force for Energy Project Recruitment. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - CIT Board Materials, 2006-2009. (Box 56, Folder 1-18)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Park Board Materials, 2006-2008. (Box 57, Folder 1-13)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Park, 2009. (Box 58, Folder 1-4)
  - Virginia Commercial Space Flight Authority (VCSEA) 2006-2009. (Box 58, Folder 5-7)
  - Virginia Early Childhood Foundation, 2006-2007. (Box 58, Folder 9-13)
  - Gulf Coast and Atlantic States Regional Task Force, 2006. (Box 60, Folder 1)